It affects one in six people in England each week, according to UK charity Mind.
据英国慈善机构Mind称，英格兰每周有六分之一的人受其影响。
That's the ratio of people who report experiencing a common mental health problem, such as depression.
这是报告拥有常见心理健康问题（如抑郁症）的人群比例。
Whether temporarily down in the dumps, or chronically depressed, many rely on anti-depressants to lift their dejected mood.
无论是暂时情绪低落，还是长期抑郁，许多人都依赖抗抑郁药来改善沮丧的心情。
But, they have a cost – one ex-user told the BBC that they felt they were in a "chemical fog" and were desperate to stop.
但这些药物有代价——一位前使用者告诉BBC，她感觉自己处于“化学迷雾”中，迫切希望停药。
If medication is a last resort, what alternatives are there when you're feeling truly blue?
如果药物是最后的手段，当你真正感到忧郁时，还有什么替代方法呢？
What about cold-water swimming to combat melancholy?
冷水游泳对抗抑郁如何？
One participant, known as Sarah, took part in the 2016 BBC One series The Doctor Who Gave Up Drugs.
一位名叫萨拉的参与者参加了2016年BBC第一频道的系列节目《放弃药物的医生》。
She had been taking anti-depressants since the age of 17.
她从17岁起就开始服用抗抑郁药。
Two years after the show, she is off all medication and still swimming – something a recent British Medical Journal report believes may be an effective treatment for depression.
节目播出两年后，她停用了所有药物，仍在游泳——最近《英国医学杂志》的一份报告认为这可能是治疗抑郁症的有效方法。
Apart from the exercise and companionship of swimmers, the cold water puts the body under stress.
除了游泳带来的锻炼和泳者们提供的陪伴，冷水会让身体处于压力之下。
With repeated immersions, the body better adapts not just to this physical stress, but mental stress, including the psychological problems of life that lead to low spirits.
通过反复浸泡，身体不仅能更好地适应这种生理压力，还能适应心理压力，包括生活中导致情绪低落的心理问题。
Susan Calman relies on kindness to brighten her mood.
苏珊・卡尔曼依靠善举来改善心情。
The 43-year-old comedian and author encourages others to use altruism to improve the lives of those around them.
这位43岁的喜剧演员兼作家鼓励他人通过利他主义改善周围人的生活。
"It can be as simple as holding open a door for someone, or giving someone a compliment, or buying someone a packet of crisps while they're feeling down," she tells the BBC.
“这可以很简单，比如为别人扶门、赞美别人，或者在别人情绪低落时给他们买一包薯片，”她告诉BBC。
In fact, anything that uplifts.
事实上，任何能让人振作的事情都行。
"If we all started to be a bit kinder then maybe we could start seeing the world as a better place.
“如果我们都开始更友善一点，也许我们会开始把世界看作一个更美好的地方。
It's really about kindness and then from that, just finding that happiness," she says.
这真的关乎善良，然后从中找到幸福，”她说。
Or you could talk about it.
或者你可以谈谈它。
Woebot is a chatbot designed to support people dealing with problems by teaching coping strategies.
Woebot是一款聊天机器人，旨在通过教授应对策略来帮助人们处理问题。
"There's a reason why good therapeutic approaches are conversational.
“优秀的治疗方法采用对话形式是有原因的。
It just asks the right questions so you can figure it out," Alison Darcy, founder of Woebot, tells the BBC.
它只是提出正确的问题，让你自己想清楚，”Woebot创始人艾莉森・达西告诉BBC。
One user, Nick Impson, explained that Woebot relieves the potential trust issues that can occur when talking to a stranger, even a qualified one.
一位用户尼克・英普森解释说，Woebot缓解了与陌生人（即使是合格的专业人士）交谈时可能出现的信任问题。
Feeling despondent happens to everyone.
每个人都会感到沮丧。
When it does, you might want to try one of these methods and see if it works for you.
当你感到沮丧时，可能想尝试这些方法中的一种，看看是否适合自己。
We hope you'll be feeling as right as rain again in no time.
我们希望你很快就会恢复健康。